Back in badness.
The Bad Guys 2 is a family, comedy, crime film directed by Pierre Perifel.
The now-reformed Bad Guys are trying (very, very hard) to be good, but instead find themselves hijacked into a
high-stakes, globe-trotting heist, masterminded by a new team of criminals they never saw coming: The Bad Girls.
Wolf (voice), played by Sam Rockwell.
Snake (voice), played by Marc Maron.
Tarantula (voice), played by Awkwafina.
Shark (voice), played by Craig Robinson.
Piranha (voice), played by Anthony Ramos.
Diane Foxington (voice), played by Zazie Beetz.
The Bad Guys 2 is a 2025 American animated heist comedy film loosely based on the children's
book series The Bad Guys by Aaron Blabey and produced by DreamWorks Animation.
The sequel to The Bad Guys (2022), it was directed by Pierre
Perifel and written by Yoni Brenner and Etan Cohen.
The film stars Sam Rockwell, Marc Maron, Awkwafina, Craig Robinson, Anthony Ramos, Zazie Beetz, Alex Borstein, Richard Ayoade, and Lilly
Singh, reprising their roles from the first film, with Danielle Brooks, Natasha Lyonne, and Maria Bakalova joining the cast.
In the film, the Bad Guys are forced to come out of retirement and join forces
with an all-female criminal squad to perform one last heist.
Perifel expressed interest on developing a sequel to The Bad Guys in
March 2022, before the release of the first film.
Two years later, DreamWorks Animation announced a sequel,
with Perifel and the voice cast returning.
Lyonne joined the cast in July 2024, with the involvement of
Brooks and Bakalova being announced in November.
Daniel Pemberton composed the score, returning from the previous film.
The Bad Guys 2 premiered in Argentina on July 24, 2025, before being
released in the United States on August 1, by Universal Pictures.
The film received positive reviews from critics and grossed $240 million.
The film explores themes of based on novel or
book, snake, wolf, spider, villain.
The tone is lighthearted.